{"data":[{"question":"Alex was made ___ as a volunteer in an orphanage for a week as a punishment.","a":"working","b":"to work","c":"to be working","d":"work","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Be made to do sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Charles Babbage is generally considered ___ the first computer.","a":"inventing","b":"to have invented","c":"having invented","d":"to invent","answer":"2","explain":"\n - Consider to be\/do sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Frank doesn't have to be told ___. He always studies hard.","a":"to learn","b":"learn","c":"learning","d":"learned","answer":"1","explain":"\n - Tell + Infinitive","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The patient was warned ___ meat after the surgery.","a":"eating not","b":"to eat not","c":"not eating","d":"not to eat","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Warn somebody not to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Ms. Du is said ___ abroad, and Jeff may know what country she studied in.","a":"to study","b":"to have studied","c":"to have been studying","d":"to be studying","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Structure: be said to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The missing boys and girls were last seen ___ near the river.","a":"to be playing","b":"playing","c":"to play","d":"play","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb_ing : you find \/see or watch part of the action","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"We agreed ___ in the front of the post office but so far he hasn't turned up yet.","a":"meeting","b":"having met","c":"to have met","d":"to meet","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Agree to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I would love ___ to the exhibition with you yesterday afternoon but I had to work extra hours to finish a case.","a":"having gone","b":"to go","c":"to have gone","d":"going","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Would like\/love to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Emily has worked with teenagers before, so she knows what ___ in her new job.","a":"to expect","b":"expected","c":"expects","d":"to be expecting","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Some verbs: ask, decide, explain, forget, know, show, tell, understand, can be followed by a question word such as where\/ how\/ what\/ who\/ when or whether + To Verb ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Joseph pretended ___ Lily when she passed by.","a":"not seeing","b":"not to see","c":"having not seen","d":"to not see","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Pretend to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}